torry.net 2011-12-31

# Torry's Delphi Pages

| 

**Privacy Policy**

* * *

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Torry's Delphi Pages** respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting your privacy throughout your use of our web site.

When you place an order online with us, we redirect you to third-party web site, provided by [ShareIt](http://www.shareit.com/privacy_statement.html). ShareIt has it own privacy policy, please read it before making an order.

We do not gather any credit card information from your product registration, we have no such technical possibility, and we do not keep any such kind of information. Moreover, we do not want to.

So, for your own privacy, please do not send us any credit card information via open channels (e.g. to our support e-mail), use this information only when placing your order via ShareIt. We do not collect any personal information from you as well.

If you subscribe to our subscription services you are required to provide your name and email address. Your name and email address will not be shared with any third party nor used for unsolicited email communication.

We use cookies on our web site only to collect general usage information, such as aggregated site-visitation statistics. A cookie is a small file that a Web site writes to your hard drive when you visit that site. A cookie is uniquely yours and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It is a kind of your ID card and can not deliver viruses. Cookies can not read information from your hard drive or read information from other cookies. Cookies are not used to collect your personal information. You can disable cookies by using Internet Options of your browser. 

Cookies help us determine what information is most valuable to you and therefore we can improve our services and the web site.

This site contains references to third parties web pages. We do not bear any responsibility for their privacy practices. To make sure your private information will be secured with them you have to read respective privacy statements of the third parties.

We reserve the right to update privacy statement from time to time. If we change privacy statement conspicuous notice will be placed on our web site.

* * *

| **News from our Sponsors**  
---  

  [Kindle, Wi-Fi, Graphite, 6 inches Display with New E Ink Pearl Technology](http://www.torry.net/advtxt/adclick.php?bannerid=159&zoneid=1&source=&dest=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB004HFS6Z0%2Fref%3Das_li_tf_tl%3Fie%3DUTF8%26tag%3Dtorrysdelphipage%26linkCode%3Das2%26camp%3D217145%26creative%3D399373%26creativeASIN%3DB004HFS6Z0)  
Kindle is our #1 bestselling item for two years running. It's also the most-wished-for, most-gifted, and has the most 5-star reviews of any product on Amazon. Now it's even better. 

  * All-New, High-Contrast E Ink Screen - 50% better contrast with latest E Ink Pearl technology 
  * Read in Bright Sunlight - No glare 
  * New and Improved Fonts - New crisper, darker fonts 
  * New Sleek Design - 21% smaller body while keeping the same 6" size reading area 
  * 17% Lighter - Only 8.5 ounces, weighs less than a paperback 
  * Battery Life of Up to Two Months - A single charge lasts up to two months with wireless off 
  * Double the Storage - Up to 3,500 books 
  * More... 

ThemeEngine is a library of components which allows to change visual appearance and behavior of your application with use of the powerful set of tools including visual components, convenient designers, easy-to-use non-visual components, the optimized graphic algorithms and a set of ready themes. ThemeEngine can add themes to forms, to the menu and to the elements of the management. 150+ stable easy to use components and 1000+ free skins.  [ more...](http://www.torry.net/advtxt/adclick.php?bannerid=69&zoneid=1&source=&dest=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.torry.net%2Fshowcase.php%3Fvn%3D13)

  [Delphi 2010 Handbook: A Guide to the New Features of Delphi 2010;](http://www.torry.net/advtxt/adclick.php?bannerid=155&zoneid=1&source=&dest=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2F1450597262%2Fref%3Das_li_qf_sp_asin_tl%3Fie%3DUTF8%26tag%3Dtorrysdelphipage%26linkCode%3Das2%26camp%3D217145%26creative%3D399377%26creativeASIN%3D1450597262)  
The guide to what's new in Delphi 2010, from the best-selling author of the Mastering Delphi series and the Delphi 2007 and 2009 Handbooks. The book covers all the new features of Delphi 2010 for Win32, from Extended RTTI to new IDE features, from Windows 7 support to the improved DataSnap architecture. This is a brand new book, there is no overlapping material with the Delphi 2007 Handbook and Delphi 2009 Handbook (which you can consider buying along with this book in printed or electronic format). The Delphi 2010 Handbook is expected to have about 300 pages covering exclusively new Delphi 2010 features. There is no introduction material or anything like that. The book is for developers who use Delphi 2010.  [ more...](http://www.torry.net/advtxt/adclick.php?bannerid=155&zoneid=1&source=&dest=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2F1450597262%2Fref%3Das_li_qf_sp_asin_tl%3Fie%3DUTF8%26tag%3Dtorrysdelphipage%26linkCode%3Das2%26camp%3D217145%26creative%3D399377%26creativeASIN%3D1450597262)

"Introducing Delphi Programming turned out to be outstanding: it begins where I needed to begin: it progresses smoothly from task to task; it is built around sets of practical exercises and practice activities; explanations are clear and well organized. It is the best "how to" book of any type that I have ever used.--Pat Byrd, Department of Applied Linguistics & ESL, Georgia State University  [ more...](http://www.torry.net/advtxt/adclick.php?bannerid=157&zoneid=1&source=&dest=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2F0195789113%2Fref%3Das_li_qf_sp_asin_tl%3Fie%3DUTF8%26tag%3Dtorrysdelphipage%26linkCode%3Das2%26camp%3D217145%26creative%3D399377%26creativeASIN%3D0195789113)  

|  |  | 

Guest Book

|
